{
    "subject": "resource/Secret_Sunshine",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "Secret Sunshine is a film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9615489840507507,
            "question": "Is Secret Sunshine a critically acclaimed film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.945598304271698,
            "question": "Is Secret Sunshine a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8699402213096619,
            "question": "Who directed Secret Sunshine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6438446640968323,
            "question": "Where was Secret Sunshine filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5516707897186279,
            "question": "Who are the main actors in Secret Sunshine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5151515007019043,
            "question": "What type of work is Secret Sunshine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46417495608329773,
            "question": "What is the main theme of Secret Sunshine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43282458186149597,
            "question": "What genre does Secret Sunshine belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33454635739326477,
            "question": "What year was Secret Sunshine released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3012818396091461,
            "question": "Has Secret Sunshine won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Secret Sunshine is a film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6809_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Secret Sunshine released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6809_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre does Secret Sunshine belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6809_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main theme of Secret Sunshine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6809_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6809_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6809_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6809_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6809_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6809_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6809_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6809_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6809_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6809_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6809_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the documents, I can say that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly describe \"Secret Sunshine\" as a film, thus supporting the statement that \"Secret Sunshine is a film.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}